A Guide to the Letters from James Branch Cabell, September 1926-December 1950
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Letters from James Branch Cabell, September 1926-December 1950
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
9199
This collection consists of ten letters.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was purchased on February 5, 1973.
Arrangement
These letters are arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- James Branch Cabell to Leon Underwood, September 9, 1926, TLS, 1 p.
- James Branch Cabell to Leon Underwood, October 23, 1926, TLS, 1 p.
- James Branch Cabell to Leon Underwood, October 31, 1926, TLS, 1 p.
- James Branch Cabell to Leon Underwood, November 6, 1926, TLS, 1 p.
- James Branch Cabell to Leon Underwood, November 27, 1926, TLS, 1 p.
- James Branch Cabell to James R. Wells, April 9, 1928, TLS, 1 p., with envelope
- James Branch Cabell to "Mr. Carroll," August 15, 1931, TLS, 1 p.
- James Branch Cabell to Robert Benaway Brown, September 18, 1950, TLS, 1 p., with envelope
- James Branch Cabell Robert Benaway Brown, December 10, 1950, TLS, 1 p., with envelope
- Cabell family to Robert Benaway Brown, December 18, 1950, Christmas card, 1 p., with envelope